Guide to the Harry H. Love papers, 1907-1964.
Love, Harry H. papers, 1907-1964.
- Pamphlets on Thailand's rice program and related subjects, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Correspondence - Cornell, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Correspondence - Cornell, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Correspondence - Cornell, 1955-1956 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Pamphlet on Paddy Fertilizer by Richard Pringle, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Agricultural memoranda, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Personnel actions, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Personnel actions, 1955-1956 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Personnel actions - travel authorizations and vouchers, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Personnel actions - housing, 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- OFAR, 1950-1953 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction - Taiwan, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction - Taiwan, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction - Taiwan, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Expense Accounts, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Personnel - rice program, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Personnel - rice program, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Personnel - rice program, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Director E. O. Sessions, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Personal Correspondence - A, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Personal Correspondence - B, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Personal Correspondence - C, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Personal Correspondence - D, 1951-1955 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Personal Correspondence - E-F, 1951-1955 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Personal Correspondence - G, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Personal Correspondence - K-I, 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Personal Correspondence - J, 1951-1956 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Personal Correspondence - K, 1951 -1956 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Personal Correspondence - L, 1951-1955 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Personal Correspondence - M, 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Personal Correspondence - N, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Personal Correspondence - O-P, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Personal Correspondence - Q, 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Personal Correspondence - R, 1951-1954 (Box 12, Folder 6l)
- Personal Correspondence - S, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Personal Correspondence - T, 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Personal Correspondence - U-V, 1951-1956 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Personal Correspondence -W-Z, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Miscellaneous, 1956 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Report of Agricultural Extension in Pakistan by C. W. Chang, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Design and Analysis of Factorial Experiments by C. L. Pan, n. d. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Papers on Rice Breeding. - Bangkok, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Papers on Rice Breeding - Bangkok, n. d. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Pamphlets re: rice in various Asiatic countries, 1950-1954 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous articles, n. d. (maps, pamphlets, citations, invitations, etc. ) (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Bogor Paper, n. d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Reference material re: Japanese Experiment Stations, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Reference material re: Japanese Experiment Stations, 1954 and n. d. (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Pamphlets on Japanese Railways, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Draft report of the 5th meeting of the IRC working party on rice breeding, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Report of the 6th meeting of the IRC working party on rice breeding, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Rice Breeding Documents (IRC/FP/ 55/6-25) and (IRC /bp/ 55/6-8), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Rice Breeding Documents (IRC /BP/ 55/1-8), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Rice Breeding Documents (IRC /BP/ 55/9-35), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Rice Breeding Documents ( IRC /BP/ 55 / 56-68 ), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Magazine on Reclamation and land improvement in Japan, 1954 (Written in Japanese) (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Magazine - "Free World, " n. d. (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Reports on Thai Rice Program, 1949-1955 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Guide books and sightseeing material for IRC delegates, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Guide books and sightseeing material for IRC delegates, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous agricultural papers and other material, 1952-1956, n. d. (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Correspondence with John H. Reisner and others re: Nanking Story, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Copy - Cornell-Nanking Story, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 31-32)
- Wong Barley, 1943, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Agriculture and Forestry Notes, Nanking, 1938-1940 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Annual Reports of College of Agriculture and Forestry, Nanking, 1924-1931 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Mss. - Report of the Department of Agronomy, Nanking (copy), 1928-1930 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Report of the second year's work on the cooperative plant improvement program, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Report on cooperative project in crop improvement (copy), 1929 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Report on cooperative project in crop improvement (copy), 1930 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Report of trip in North China, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Final Report - Plant Improvement Project, C. H. Myers, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Resources, Reports, Plans for Chinese Agriculture, 1927-1930 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Love to China - contract with government surveys and research, 1925-1934 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Schools, students, outline of research work, plans for improvement in China (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Correspondence concerning the retirement of H. H. Love (Box 14, Folder 1)
- China Program, July-Sept., 1949 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction (JCRR), 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- E. G. A. China Program, 1936-1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- E. G. A. China Program, ca. 1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Photographs, ca. 1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Taiwan Agriculture and Forestry Monthly. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Pamphlet re: Chinese Rice improvement stations, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Report on Chinese Experimental and Extension work, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Extension of rice seed in Taiwan, n. d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Seed problems in Taiwan (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Notes: University of Nanking, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Hu Shih's Introduction to T. H. Shen's Struggle of a Chinese Farm Boy (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with Shen, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Seed Problems in Taiwan (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Printed Matter - China, 1925, 1926, 1937, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Thailand Papers, correspondence, 1949, 1951-1952, 1954-1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Thailand Papers, ca. 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Thailand Papers, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Correspondence between R. J. Borden of Hawaiian Ext. and Love, 1933-1939 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, Borden and Love, 1934-1942 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Honolulu Data, statistics, blank experiments, Association of Hawaiian Sugar -Technologists, Correspondence and Blue Prints, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Honolulu Data, Statistics, Notes on Interpretation of Experiment Results, Blue Prints, Field Experiments (35 pp.), c 1931 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Printed Matter, 1926-1942 (Box 14, Folder 24-26)
- Correspondence with G. W. Shepherd, 1935-1937; E. E. Carey Fund, 1935-1936 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1914, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Correspondence after retirement, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1961-1964, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Clippings from The Globe and Mail, Toronto, July 28, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Comments on Dr. Love's Book, 1943-1949 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Shen, T. H., 1926-1935 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Shen, T. H., 1936-1948 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Shen, T. H., 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Reports, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Love - Personal to Dean Myers, 1948-1949 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- H. H. Love, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- H. H. Love, 1943-1962 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- William I. Meyers - Papers, 1962, n. d. (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Five Year Report, Famine Prevention Report, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- From files on graduate students - Shen, H. T., 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- From files on graduate students - Shen, H. T., 1927-1929 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Reports of Cooperative Project Project, China, 1925-1930 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Departmental Matters, 1944-1948 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Correspondence with Dr. Love - China and Puerto Rico, 1931-1932 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with Dr. Love - China and Puerto Rico, 1933-1940 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with Dr. Love - China and Puerto Rico, 1934-1937 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with Dr. Love - China and Puerto Rico, 1936-1941 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Special, 1934-1935 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Final Report, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence and Reports for History of Cornell-Nanking Cooperative Plant Improvement Project, 1932-1962 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Photographs of China (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
- Negatives (Box 15, Folder 13)
- 2 Scrapbooks - Fraternity (Tau Kappa Epsilon) The Standard (Newspaper for International Readers) (Box 16)